CURRICULUM VITAE

(a) PERSONAL DETAILS

NAME: NYANGOMA ESTHER

Date of Birth: 25th December 2002

Nationality: Ugandan

Marital Status : Single

E-mail: Essieelsie@g.mail.com

Telephone: 07022993713/0775054107

(b) PERSONAL PROFILE

I am energetic and ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake or situation I am presented with.

As a graduate with two years experience in computer science, I am excellent in working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence.

(c) EDUCATION BACKGROUND

| Period | Institution/School | Award |
|-----------|-------------------------------|---------------------|
| 2008-2014 | Community Primary School | PLE |
| 2015-2018 | St. Margrate College Makerere | UCE |
| 2019-2021 | Kampala High School | UACE |
| 2022-2024 | YMCA Comprehensive | Diploma in Computer |
| | Institute | Science |

(d) EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

| Period | Organization | Position/Duties |
|-----------|--------------------------|-----------------------|
| 2013 | Community Primary School | Class Monitress |
| 2016-2017 | St. Margrate College | Speaker |
| | Makerere | |
| 2019-2020 | Kampala high School | Entrepreneurship Club |
| | | President |

(e) HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

| LANGUAGE PROFICIENO | C |
|---------------------------|---|
| Listening to music. | |
| Making new friends. | |
| Travelling to new places. | |
| Playing soccer and tennis | |
| Reading online novels. | |

(f) CY

English

Luganda

Kiswahili

Korean

(g) REFEREES(at least three):

Mukisa martha - 07585633332

Mr. Kavuma Peter -0752627774

Academic Registrar (YMCA) - 0414-233-294/0414-232-856

(h) **DECLARTION**

I **Nyangoma Esther** certify to the best of my knowledge and understanding that; the particulars given here in are true and correct in all aspects.

NYANGOMA ESTHER

Nyangoma esther.